seonitronetwork.com 2008-06-16

# OUR PRIVACY POLICY

**Privacy Policy - Revised and Effective 23 June 2006**

By visiting this web site you are accepting the practices described in ****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** Privacy Policy.

All websites operated by **SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**. is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors.

Please be aware that we appreciate the trust you place in us by providing information on this web site, and our commitment to you is to use this information with both care and sensitivity. The information we collect from visitors to our web site helps us continually improve the products we offer to our valued customers. Types of information collected are outlined as follows:

  * Any information you voluntarily enter on our web site, which may include your name, mailing and e-mail addresses, telephone numbers and other personal information, is maintained and may be utilized by ****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** to help us improve our web site and to identify, improve and promote products and services in which you may have an interest. This information may be shared with 3rd parties for marketing purposes. 
  * In addition, we use cookies (as do the vast majority of other companies that do business on the World Wide Web) when you visit our site, which are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your web browser. Information we collect and analyze via cookies includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system and platform, date and time of your visit, and cookie number. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, please review the options listed in the Help portion of the toolbar on your computer. The toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. Blog-Power.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.

Check out the FTC's website:

<http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html> for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.

****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** periodically sends email offers, or authorizes others to send e-mail offers, to its web site visitors on behalf of other vendors and advertisers with whom we have a business association or relationship. By providing information on this web site, you are agreeing to receive these periodic e-mail offers, which ****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** believes may be of interest to you as a consumer. If you do not wish to receive e-mail offers from us, please be sure to scroll down to the bottom of the first e-mail you receive and click on the opt-out link provided, which will remove your e-mail address from our database. You will then receive no further e-mail communications from us. If you do not scroll down to the bottom of the first e-mail you receive (or any e-mails thereafter), you will continue to receive e-mail offers from ****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** until you choose to click on the opt-out link that will be provided in each e-mail you receive from us.

We will release account and other personal information when such release is necessary to comply with any state, federal or international laws, or when, in our judgment, we determine it to be necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of ****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** or our valued customers. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

Please note that ****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** web site uses secure payment processing software that encrypts all financial information you input when you place an order. Any and all financial transactions you make through our payment systems will be protected while you are doing business on our web site. If you have any concern about privacy at ****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** web site, please contact us at [support @ seonitronetwork.com](mailto:support%20@%20seonitro.com) (note to customer: please remove spaces before e-mailing), and we will make every effort to address your inquiry in a timely manner.

****SEONITRO.COM BY Dori Friend / SEONitro, LLC**** reserves the right to add to, delete from or in any other way modify any or all of this Privacy Policy without prior notification. Changes to this Privacy Policy shall be noticed by posting a revised Privacy Policy and its effective date on our web site.
